A Finding Aid to the Fendrick Gallery Records, 1952-2001, in the Archives of American Art AAA.fendgall
Archives of American Art
- Commissioned Works and Projects, 1972-2000, undated; Series 3; (Boxes 54-57; 3.5 linear feet)
  - Paley, Albert (Box 56)
    - First F. A. Building, Dupont Centre, Orlando, Fla., 1989 (Box 56)
    - Gateways Committee, Springfield Central, Inc., Springfield, Mass., 1986-1989 (Box 56)
    - Hospital for Sick Children, Washington, D.C., 1993 (Box 56)
    - Interior Gates for Sausalito, Cal. House, Robinson, Mills Williams, Architects, San Francisco, Calif., 1986-1988 (Box 56)
    - Le Madri Restaurant, Hickok-Warner Architects, Washington, D.C., 1992 (Box 56)
    - Leu Botanical Gardens, Orlando, Fla., 1989-1990 (Box 56)
    - Miscellaneous Commission Proposals, 1981-1999, undated; (6 folders) (Box 56)
    - Naples/Marco Philharmonic Theater, Naples, Fla., 1989 (Box 56)
    - Orlando City Hall, City of Orlando Arts Advisory Board, Orlando, Fla., 1990-1992, undated (Box 56)
    - Philadelphia Redevelopment Authority, Philadelphia, Pa., 1982-1983 (Box 56)
    - Promenade Two Building, Promenade Two Limited Partnership, Atlanta, Ga., 1989-1991 (Box 56)
    - Seattle Arts Commission, Seattle, Wash., 1983-1985 (Box 56)
    - Two White Flint North, Lerner Enterprises, Rockville, Md., 1992 (Box 56)
    - United Services Automobile Assoc. (USAA), Mid-Atlantic Regional Office (MARO) Building, Cary Ellis Co., Norfolk, Va., 1991-1992 (Box 56)
    - U. S. Fidelity and Guaranty Co. (U. S. F. & G.) Building, Baltimore, Md. 1989-1991, undated (Box 56)
  - Pedestrian Bridge Project ("Garage 49"), Bethesda, Montgomery County Art in Public Architecture, Rockville, Md., 1986-1987 (Box 56)
  - Percent for Art Program (Box 56)
    - Alaska State Office Building, Alaska State Council on the Arts, Anchorage, Alaska (Paley), 1983-1985 (Box 56)
    - Capital Projects, Municipality of Anchorage, Anchorage, Alaska, (Paley), 1984-1985 (Box 56)
    - Central State University, C. J. McLin Project, Ohio Arts Council, Columbus, Ohio, 1992-1993 (Box 56)
    - Criminal Justice Center Project, City of Philadelphia, Philadelphia, Pa., (Kaskey, Paley), 1987-1992 (Box 56)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs of NYC, New York, N.Y., (Dreyfuss), 1985, 1997) (Box 56)
    - Intermediate School #218, Manhattan, City of New York, New York, N. Y., (Paley), 1985-1986 (Box 56)
    - Miscellaneous Projects, 1976-1994 (Box 56)
    - Ohio Arts Council Projects, Columbus, Ohio, (Dusenbery, Gilliam, Kaskey, Paley), 1990-1999 (Box 56)
    - Phoenix Art Commission, Cit of Phoenix, Phoenix, Ariz., 1988 (Box 56)
    - Stuyvesant High School, Battery Park, City of New York, New York, N.Y., 1988 (Box 56)
    - Twenty-third Street Station, Lexington Avenue Line, Manhattan, Metropolitan Transit Authority, New York, N.Y.,(Paley),1984 (Box 56)
    - Virginia Beach Arts Center, City of Virginia Beach, Virginia Beach, Va., (Paley), 1989 (Box 56)
  - Philadelphia International Airport, Percent For Art Program, Philadelphia, Pa., (Sam Gilliam), 1994-1995, undated (Box 57)
  - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey Art Project Proposals, New York, N.Y., 1987-1990, undated (Box 57)
  - Public Arts Commission at Portland International Airport, Metropolitan Arts Commission, Portland, Ore., 1993 (Box 57)
  - Shea Boulevard Project, Public Art Program for the City of Scottsdale, Scottsdale, Ariz., (Kaskey, Paley), 1992 (Box 57)
  - Southeast Financial Center, Tampa, Fla., 1990-1991, undated (Box 57)
  - Truland Corporation Projects, North Arlington, Va., 1987-1989 (Box 57)
  - U .S. General Services Administration, Art-In-Architecture Program (Box 57)
    - Drake, John, 1988-1998; (2 folders) (Box 57)
    - Dreyfuss, John, 1983-1995 (Box 57)
    - Dusenbery, Walter, 1987-1993 (Box 57)
    - Forrester, Patricia Tobacco, 1986-1995 (Box 57)
    - General Information, 1977-1983, 1986-1992, undated; (2 folders) (Box 57)
    - Kaskey Raymond, 1983-1995, undated; (4 folders) (Box 57)
  - U .S. General Services Administration, Art-In-Architecture Program (Box 57)
    - Meadmore, Clement, 1991-1998 (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1977, 1986-1993 (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous Projects/Proposals, 1987, 1995-1999; (2 folders) (Box 57)
    - Moore, Arthur Cotton, 1990-1992 (Box 57)
    - Paley, Albert, Miscellaneous Proposals, 1979-1995, undated (Box 57)
    - Paley, Albert, Michael U. S. Courthouse, Camden, N.J., 1992-1994 (Box 57)
    - Piccillo, Joseph, 1990-1994 (Box 57)
  - World War II Memorial, National Capital Planning Commission, 1999 (Box 57)
- Exhibition Files, 1961, 1970-1996, undated; Series 4; (Box 58-63; 5.5 linear ft.)
  Files documenting Fendrick gallery and Barbara Fendrick Gallery exhibitions. Series 4.2, Exhibition Files contain a wide variety of materials documenting exhibitions, such as correspondence, price lists, notes, shipping records, drafts and printed copies of exhibit text, publicity, and other printed material. The Exhibition Files are arranged chronologically by year of exhibit, followed by title of the exhibition. The span dates at the end of each entry describe the dating of materials within the folder. The Special Projects' Files concern other art-related events and special exhibitions in which the gallery participated.
  Researchers should take note that Series 6, Subject Files also contains additional information on some of the larger or recurring theme exhibits produced by the Fendrick galleries. For example, the "Book Art" and "Book Artists" records of Subject Files contain additional information on planning the gallery's four book arts shows. Further information on exhibitions may also be found under Artists Files and in the Administrative Records.
  Arrangement note
  The Exhibition Files series is arranged into the following subseries:
  4.1: Announcements and Catalogs, 1974-1993
  4.2: Exhibition Files, 1961, 1970-1994
  4.3: Special Projects, 1973-1996
  - Announcements and Catalogs, 1974-1993; 4.1
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1972-1993, undated; (4 folders) (Box 58)
  - Exhibition Files, 1961, 1970-1994; 4.2
    - 1971, The Contemporary Art of Banners (Nov.9-Dec. 4), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1970-1971, undated (Box 58)
    - 1973, Baby Blocks and Roman Squares, Quilt Show (June-July), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1971-1984, undated; (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - 1973, The North American Indian (Mar. 13-Apr. 21), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1972-1976, undated (Box 58)
    - 1974, Indian Miniatures and Ikats (Feb. 12-Mar. 9), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1973-1979, undated (Box 58)
    - 1974, The Soft Pencil Line (Apr. 30-May 18), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1973-1974, undated (Box 58)
    - 1975, Clay, USA (Mar. 11-Apr. 12), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1974-1975; (4 folders) (Box 58)
    - 1975, Fifteen from the Corcoran Biennale (May 22-June 14), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1975, undated (Box 58)
    - 1976, American Folk Art Today (Mar. 116-Apr. 17), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1975-1984, undated; (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - 1976, The Book as Art (Jan. 12-Feb. 14), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1972-1979, undated; (5 folders) (Box 59)
    - 1976, Classic American Quilts (Feb. 18-Mar. 17), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1975-1983, undated (Box 59)
    - 1976, Limited Edition Artists' Books (Nov. 30-Dec. 31), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. (Box 59)
    - 1977, The American Table (Mar. 17--Apr. 16), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1976-1979, undated; (8 folders) (Box 59)
    - 1977, The Book as Art II (Feb. 15-Mar.12), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1975-1978, 1984, undated; (4 folders) (Box 59)
    - 1977, Wish I Were There: American Landscape Watercolors and Drawings (Jan. 10-Feb. 5), Fendrick Gallery Records, Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1976-1977, undated (Box 59)
    - 1978, Boyd and Evans: Photographs (June 20-Aug. 18), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. (Box 60)
    - 1978, Carol Summers: Woodcuts (June 20-Aug. 18), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. (Box 60)
    - 1978, Garbage & Wrecks (June 20-Aug. 18), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1975-1979, undated (Box 60)
    - 1978, New Works by Bill Suworoff (Dec.), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. (Box 60)
    - 1979, The Book as Art III (Mar. 5-Apr. 6), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1976-1983, undated; (6 folders) (Box 60)
    - 1979, Contradictions (July 9-Sept. 8), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1978-1980, undated (Box 60)
    - 1979, The Peaceable Kingdom (May 15-June 23), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1971-1983, undated (Box 60)
    - 1980, Couples, Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1977, 1980 (Box 60)
    - 1980, Gone Wild: New Paintings by James Pernotto (Mar. 11-Apr. 5), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. (Box 60)
    - 1980, H. Terry Braunstein: Books (Mar. 11-Apr. 5), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1974-1982, undated (Box 60)
    - 1980, Sandra Freckleton Watercolor Exhibit (Jan. 15-Feb. 9), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1979 (Box 60)
    - 1980, Washington Color School Revisited: The Sixties (Sept. 9-Oct. 4), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1961-1982, undated; (3 folders) (Box 60)
    - 1980, Wendell Castle: Furniture as Art II (Nov. 5-29), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. (Box 60)
    - 1981, Graphic Arts in America (November), Fendrick Gallery loan to USICA, Belgrade, Yugoslavia, 1981-1983 (Box 60)
    - 1980, Joke van Ommen: Jewelry (June 9-July 3), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1981 (Box 60)
    - 1980, Miluše_Roubi ková-Kytková: Works in Glass (May 28-June 19), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1981 (Box 60)
    - 1980, Portraits of the Artists (Feb. 3-28), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1973-1983, undated (Box 60)
    - 1980, Three From Prague: Masters of Czech Glass (May 28-June 19), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1981-1983; (2 folders) (Box 60)
    - 1982, Genna Watson: Sleepers (Apr. 7-May 1), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. (Box 61)
    - 1982, 25th Anniversary of Universal Limited Art Editions (May 22-June 12 and July 14-31), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1977, 1982 (Box 61)
    - 1983, American Living National Treasures (May 4-June 18), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1981-1983, undated; (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - 1983, The Art of Still Life (Jan. 15-Feb. 18), Fendrick Gallery, 1982-1983, undated; (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - 1983, First International Water Sculpture Competition Finalists (Oct. 27-Nov. 26), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1982-1984, undated; (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - 1983, Ornamentalism: The New Decorativeness in Architecture and Design (July 1-Aug. 1), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1982-1984, undated; (3 folders) (Box 61)
    - 1984, The Art of Still Life II (Mar.7-Apr. 13), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1983-1984, undated; (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - 1984, The Garden: Concepts and Realities (July 18-Sept. 11), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1979-1984, undated; (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - 1985, Alfred De Credico (Apr. 2-27), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1985-1988, undated; (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - 1985, Excellence in Architecture: D.C./AIA Award Winners (Sept. 6-Oct. 12), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. (Box 61)
    - 1985, The School of Wendell Castle: The Art of Handmade Furniture ( Aug.[?]-Sept. 2), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. (Box 61)
    - 1985, Washington Figurative Sculpture (Jan. 2-Feb. 16), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1984-1986, undated; (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - 1985, Washington Perceived: The Artist Views the Nation's Capital (Sept. 6-Oct. 12), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1973, 1985, undated (Box 61)
    - 1985, A Washington Selection: Ten Artists (May 28-June 15), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1985, undated (Box 61)
    - 1986, The Artist Obsessed: Architecture Perceived (Mar. 12-Apr. 19), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1977, 1984-1986, undated (Box 61)
    - 1986, Cleveland Print Fair (Sept. 13, 1986), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. (Box 61)
    - 1986, Fine Prints and Drawings: A Representative Sample from the Fendrick Gallery Inventory (Dec. 17, 1985-Jan. 15, 1986), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1984-1985 (Box 61)
    - 1986, Sole-ly Fish (July 30-Sept. 15), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1985-1986, undated; (2 folders) (Box 62)
    - 1987, American Folk Art: 19th Century Weathervanes (Dec. 9, 1986-Jan. 8, 1987), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1985-1988, undated; (3 folders) (Box 62)
    - 1987, Four Innovators (Apr. 22-May 2), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. (Box 62)
    - 1988, Sculpture in Architecture (May 11-21), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, New York, N.Y. (Box 62)
    - 1989, Albert Paley: Sculpture/Architectural Projects (Mar. 22-Apr. 22), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. and (Apr. 27-June 17), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1987-1989 (Box 62)
    - 1989, Bill Suworoff: Year of the Duck Dragon (Sept. 6-30), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, New York, N.Y. (Box 62)
    - 1989, Contemporary Master Prints (Jan.-Feb.), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C. and Master Prints of the 1960s and 1970s (Dec. 1988-Jan. 1989), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1989-1992 (Box 62)
    - 1989, I Wish I Were There... (June 21-July 31), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, New York, N.Y. (Box 62)
    - 1989, Kid Stuff (July 11-Sept. 9), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1988-1989; (2 folders) (Box 62)
    - 1989, Memory & Artifact: Romanticism Revisited (Sept. 6-30), Washington, D.C. and (Oct. 11-Nov. 11), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1989-1990; (2 folders) (Box 62)
    - 1990, Arthur Cotton Moore: Industrial Baroque (Feb. 20-Mar. 31), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, New York, N.Y. and (Apr. 5-28) Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1989-1992, undated (Box 62)
    - 1990, The Book as Art/The Book in Art (June 12-July 31), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1976, 1988-1991, undated; (4 folders) (Box 62)
    - 1990, The Book as Art/The Book in Art (June 12-July 31), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1976, 1988-1991, undated; (3 folders) (Box 63)
    - 1990, Drawing the Line (Dec. 1989-Jan. 19, 1990), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1989-1990 (Box 63)
    - 1990, Flâneur/Flâneuse: Out For a Stroll (May 4-31), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, New York, N.Y. (Box 63)
    - 1990, Gender: Out of the Garden (Oct. 13-Nov. 10), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, New York, 1987-1991, undated; (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - 1990, Sculpture 90 (June-July), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., 1990, undated (Box 63)
    - 1991, James Drake (Nov. 17, 1990-Jan. 4, 1991), Barbara Fendrick Gallery, 1990-1991 (Box 63)
    - 1991, Joyce Tenneson (Feb. 12-Mar. 16), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., circa 1991 (Box 63)
    - 1991, Three Romantic Realists: Steven Assael, Michael Flanagan, Derek James (May-June), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., circa 1991 (Box 63)
    - 1991, William Suworoff: Blooming Ducks (Dec. 13, 1990--Jan. 13, 1991), Fendrick Gallery, Washington, D.C., circa 1991 (Box 63)
    - 1993, Off the Mall: Inside Washington's Foremost Art Galleries (Sept. 15-Oct. 16), Museum of the Americas, Washington, D.C. (Box 63)
    - 1994, Off the Mall II (Nov. 19-Dec. 26), Hemicycle Gallery, Corcoran Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C. (Box 63)
  - Special Projects, 1973-1996; 4.3
    - Art Against Aids Exhibit, 1990 (Box 63)
    - Art on the 7th Floor Exhibit, 1996 (Box 63)
    - Artists' Rights Today Exhibition, 1975-1980 (Box 63)
    - Columns (Proposed Exhibit), 1979-1991, undated (Box 63)
    - Contemporary American Prints, Williamsburg Restoration, Inc., undated (Box 63)
    - Fendrick at Foster (Oct. 4-25), Foster Gallery, University of Wisconsin/Eau Claire, 1989-1991 (Box 63)
    - Holiday Bake Sale, 1974, undated (Box 63)
    - Hospital for Sick Children Garden Show, 1994-1995 (Box 63)
    - Livres d'Artistes, Centre Pompidou, Paris, France, 1980-1985 (Box 63)
    - Traveling Book Show (Proposed Exhibit), 1973-1986, undated; (6 folders) (Box 63)
    - Wooden Objects (Proposed Exhibit), 1983, undated (Box 63)
- Museums and Galleries Files, 1952-2000, undated; Series 5; (Box 64-72, OV 114; 9.25 linear feet)
  The gallery's relationships with other galleries, museums, institutions, and art organizations is documented in this series. Many of the files concern loans, exhibition venues, and joint exhibitions or projects. This series is comprised of two subseries. Within each subseries the files are arranged alphabetically by geographic location. Within the individual folders the material is generally arranged chronologically by year.
  5.1: Domestic Museums and Galleries, 1952-2000, undated
  5.2: International Museums and Galleries, 1967-1991, undated
  - Domestic Museums and Galleries, 1952-2000, undated; 5.1
    - Alabama (Box 64)
      - Birmingham Museum of Art, Birmingham, Ala., 1971-1990, undated (Box 64)
      - Montgomery Museum of Fine Arts, Montgomery, Ala., 1961-1984 (Box 64)
    - Arizona (Box 64)
      - Harlan Gallery, Tucson, Ariz., 1977, undated (Box 64)
      - Phoenix Art Museum, Phoenix, Ariz., 1975-1976, 1985 (Box 64)
      - Scottsdale Center for the Arts, Scottsdale, Ariz., 1991 (Box 64)
    - Arkansas, Little Rock, Miscellaneous Galleries, 1975-1987, undated (Box 64)
    - California (Box 64)
      - American Institute of Architects, San Francisco, Calif./ADI Gallery, San Francisco, Calif., 1974-1980, 1988, undated (Box 64)
      - Arion Press, San Francisco, Calif., 1988 (Box 64)
      - Braunstein Galleries, San Francisco, Calif., 1979-1983, undated (Box 64)
      - Cirrus Editions, Ltd., Los Angeles, Calif., 1980-1982 (Box 64)
      - Crown Point Press, Oakland, Calif., 1981-1988, undated (Box 64)
      - Gemini G. E. L., Los Angeles, Calif., 1978-1989, undated (Box 64)
      - Hansen-Fuller Gallery, San Francisco, Calif., 1975-1984, undated (Box 64)
      - Hirsh/Bodner and Associates, Santa Monica, Calif./18th Street Gallery, Santa Monica, Calif., 1983-1987, undated (Box 64)
      - Jim Berggruen Gallery, San Francisco, Calif., 1970-1985, undated; (2 folders) (Box 64)
      - Los Angeles, Miscellaneous Galleries, 1969-1970-1994, undated (Box 64)
      - Louise Allrich Gallery, San Francisco, Calif., 1978 (Box 64)
      - Meyer/Bloom Gallery, Santa Monica, Calif., 1990 (Box 64)
      - Miscellaneous Cities, 1977-1985, 1990-1991 (Box 64)
      - San Francisco/Northern California, Miscellaneous Galleries, 1969-1987, undated (Box 64)
    - Colorado, Miscellaneous Cities, 1975-1985, 1992-1994, undated (Box 64)
    - Connecticut (Box 64)
      - State of Connecticut Commission on the Arts, Hartford, Conn., 1986 (Box 64)
      - Yale University Art Gallery, New Haven, Conn., 1983-1977 (Box 64)
    - Delaware Art Museum/Delaware State Arts Council, Wilmington, Del., 1978-1986, undated (Box 64)
    - District of Columbia (Box 65)
      - Alexander and Alexander Services, Inc., 1986-1988 (Box 65)
      - The Anco Corporation, 1984 (Box 65)
      - American Institute of Architects, 1985, undated (Box 65)
      - American Medical Association (See also OV 114), 1979-1982, undated (Box 65)
      - Art in Embassies, 1981-1991, undated (Box 65)
      - Art Society of the International Monetary Fund, 1971-1984, undated (Box 65)
      - The Collector, 1987, undated (Box 65)
      - Corcoran Gallery, 1975-1985, undated (Box 65)
      - Diane Brown Gallery, 1977-1978, 1980-1981, undated (Box 65)
      - Dimock Gallery, George Washington University, 1977, 1980 (Box 65)
      - Federal Reserve, 1963-1964, 1975-1989, undated (Box 65)
      - Gallaudet University, 1983 (Box 65)
      - Hellmuth, Obata, and Kassabaum, 1985-1986, undated (Box 65)
      - International Communication Agency, 1981-1982, 1986, undated (Box 65)
      - International Sculpture Center, 1990, undated (Box 65)
      - Jane Haslem Gallery, 1975-1990, undated (Box 65)
      - Jean Efron, Art Consultants, 1986-1990, undated (Box 65)
      - Library of Congress, 1959-1979, 1983-1985, undated (Box 65)
      - Middendorf Gallery, 1980, 1984-1989 (Box 65)
      - Miscellaneous Galleries, 1984-2000, undated (Box 65)
      - National Academy of Sciences, 1966, 1973, undated (Box 65)
      - National Building Museum, 1988-1997 (Box 65)
      - National Endowment for the Arts, 1971-1987 (Box 65)
      - National Gallery of Art, 1961-1993, undated (Box 65)
      - National Museum of Women in the Arts, 1982 (Box 65)
      - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co., 1979, undated (Box 65)
      - The Phillips Collection, 1985 (Box 65)
      - Public Art Trust, 1983-1985, undated (Box 65)
      - Sellers, Connor & Cuneo, 1979-1980, undated (Box 65)
      - Smithsonian Institution, Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, 1974-1986, undated (Box 65)
      - Smithsonian Institution, Miscellaneous, 1981-1987 (Box 66)
      - Smithsonian Institution, National Collection of Fine Arts, 1962-1987, undated; (2 folders) (Box 66)
      - Smithsonian Institution, National Portrait Gallery, 1986 (Box 66)
      - Smithsonian Institution, Renwick Gallery, 1976-1994, undated (Box 66)
      - Smithsonian Institution, Traveling Exhibition Service, 1980-1994 (Box 66)
      - The Saunders Company, 1985 (Box 66)
      - The Vice President's House, Joan Mondale, 1979-1980, undated (Box 66)
      - Veterans Administration, Art-in-Architecture Program, 1980 (Box 66)
      - Washington Art Dealers Association, 1991-1993, undated (Box 66)
    - Florida (Box 66)
      - Federal Reserve Bank, Jacksonville, Fla., 1990 (Box 66)
      - Fort Lauderdale, Miscellaneous, 1979-1986, undated (Box 66)
      - Miami Branch, Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta, Miami, Fla., 1979 (Box 66)
      - Miami Dade Center, Miami, Fla., 1975-1982, undated; (2 folders) (Box 66)
      - Miami Dade Center, Miami, Fla., Miscellaneous, 1980-1986, undated (Box 66)
      - Miami, Miscellaneous, 1977-1983, undated (Box 66)
      - Miami, Miscellaneous Galleries, 1979-1988. undated (Box 66)
      - Miscellaneous Cities, 1975-1987, 1992, undated (Box 66)
      - Polk Museum of Art, Lakeland, Fla., 1995-1996 (Box 66)
      - University of South Florida, Tampa, Fla., 1980-1981 (Box 66)
    - Georgia (Box 66)
      - Atlanta, Miscellaneous, 1980-1985, undated (Box 66)
      - 14th Street Gallery, Atlanta, Ga., 1988 (Box 66)
      - University of Georgia, Georgia Museum of Art, Athens, Ga., 1973-1984, undated (Box 66)
    - Hawaii, Honolulu Academy of Arts, Contemporary Arts Center, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1980-1993, undated (Box 66)
    - Idaho, Boise Gallery of Art, Boise, Idaho, 1983-1984 (Box 66)
    - Illinois (Box 67)
      - Art Institute of Chicago, Chicago, Ill., 1963, 1976-1984, undated (Box 67)
      - Chicago International Art Exposition, Chicago, Ill., 1983-1984, undated (Box 67)
      - Chicago, Miscellaneous Galleries, 1963-1964, 1977-1985, 1997, undated (Box 67)
      - Exhibit A, Chicago, Ill., 1978-1985, undated (Box 67)
      - Landfall Press, Chicago, Ill., 1988-1989 (Box 67)
      - Mary and Leigh Block Gallery, Northwestern University, Gallery of American Ceramics, Evanston, Ill., 1976, 1993-1996, undated (Box 67)
    - Indiana (Box 67)
      - Indianapolis Museum of Art, Indianapolis, Ind., 1971, 1975-1986, undated (Box 67)
      - Indiana University, Bloomington, Ind., 1963, 1969-1977, 1981-1985, undated (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous Galleries, 1963, 1974-1976, 1980, 1980, undated (Box 67)
    - Iowa (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous, 1974-1986, undated (Box 67)
      - University of Iowa Museum of Art, Iowa City, Iowa, 1972-1984, undated (Box 67)
    - Kansas, University of Kansas, Lawrence, Kans., 1976, 1984, undated (Box 67)
    - Kentucky (Box 67)
      - Centre College, Danville, Ky., 1985 (Box 67)
      - University of Kentucky, Lexington, Ky., 1978, undated (Box 67)
      - Western Kentucky University, Bowling Green, Ky., 1974-1977, undated (Box 67)
    - Louisiana (Box 67)